[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But there are just so many poses and programs !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"poses\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"( I know , ignorant question ) Then why call them , or any other phonies ' Christians ' , even if they themselves claim the appellation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"claim\", does the participant \"appellation\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"First room had used tissues next to the bed and I requested it be rectified .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rectified\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have to mention that i recently separated the father into another cage close to the ' nest cage ' because he and the mother were fighting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"separated\", does the participant \"father\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Across the United States , the northern edge of species ' range is expanding , \" she said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expanding\", does the participant \"edge\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Justin , I have no knowledge of any bad faith actins Enron has pending in Texas but I will call Richard Sanders who manages domestic litgation here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manages\", does the participant \"Sanders\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The US lost yet another helicopter to hostile fire near Habbaniyah in the Sunni heartland , but this time the crew was safe .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"helicopter\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"From my first encounter at check in to my regrettable check out I found the staff and facility to exceed my expectation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"staff\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I hope you have a great summer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We oppose the use of sacred texts and religious traditions to deny legal equity to same - gender couples .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"oppose\", does the participant \"use\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i think Miramar was a famous goat trainer or something .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Brass melts at just under 2000 F which is a bright yellow heat , not red hot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"melts\", does the participant \"Brass\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Both India and Afghanistan deny the claim .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deny\", does the participant \"claim\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"On the one hand , the IPN report agreed \" Climate models generally predict that the temperature rises in the Arctic will substantially exceed the global rise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"exceed\", does the participant \"rise\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We understand that the pipe fitters are also planning to picket the Lake Worth , Florida project as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"planning\", does the participant \"fitters\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He said the main aim of the subpoenas will be to determine whether collusion occurred to \" fix \" prices , which would violate federal trade laws .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"prices\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These changes are occurring across all species , Parmesan told UPI 's Climate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"occurring\", does the participant \"changes\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The store manager , Jim Smith , made an excellent tire recommendation for my newly acquired Lexus .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"recommendation\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed working with you and wish you the best of everything .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"best\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Attached is the revised draft paper that reflects our conference call with Bob Fagan earlier this week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"paper\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The next day i took it to 2 auto shops and they both told me the same thing , engine is junk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This place had the worst tasting pizza I have ever tasted it was possible the worst food I 've ever eaten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"place\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A pattern of arrests and seizures indicate that arms are brought by the LTTE from Laos , Cambodia and Thailand into Chittagong , from where they are transported northward by land to Bhutan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brought\", does the participant \"arms\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"KENNEDY filed an opinion concurring in part , in which SOUTER , GINSBURG , and BREYER joined as to Parts I and II .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"opinion\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I saw a site that charges $ 0.70 per mile .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"site\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I read an Article in Time magazine accusing the Iranian Government of being willing to start a nuclear war and I sympathise with the Article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"read\", does the participant \"Article\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Cindy said Jaime has grown up very much .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grown\", does the participant \"Jaime\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I expect that many of the displaced people ( those affluent and those not ) will remain in the places they were evacuated to .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"evacuated\", does the participant \"they\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Last month , Nasrallah announced that his party would close ranks with Hamas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"close\", does the participant \"ranks\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The work was completed within one week , and everything was cleaned up on completion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cleaned\", does the participant \"everything\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need responses or direction by no later than COB on Monday , October 30 , 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"We\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Yahoo! Mail has the best spam protection around\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"protection\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This entity was created in 2000 for the acquistion of WarpSpeed Communications ( now Enron WarpSpeed Services , Inc. 83N ) , and then dissolved upon completion of merger .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"created\", does the participant \"entity\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There is nothing wrong with a REAL negotiation , but nothing particularly helpful about generating one that s just for show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"generating\", does the participant \"one\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a question about McDonald 's Monopoly !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"question\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This entity was created in 2000 for the acquistion of WarpSpeed Communications ( now Enron WarpSpeed Services , Inc. 83N ) , and then dissolved upon completion of merger .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"created\", does the participant \"entity\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You need either a filter for each device except the DSL modem , or a whole home filter which filters all the jacks , except the one which the DSL modem connects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filters\", does the participant \"filter\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the participant \"refinery\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a routine surgery for an ingrown toenail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"you play too much cod ;P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the participant \"you\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"laptop\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I hope you do n't change your mind about going to the wedding Sunday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"mind\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I left you a voice mail on Friday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"mail\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The work was completed within one week , and everything was cleaned up on completion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cleaned\", does the participant \"everything\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I see the merit in flowing with duality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"see\", does the participant \"merit\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My brother said they only had full - auto and semiautomatic during Vietnam .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"brother\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Huge amounts of money , which could have solved many social problems in this dysfunctional part of the world , are channeled into three concentric spheres supporting death and murder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"solved\", does the participant \"amounts\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They called and worked with me to fix it so that it would look perfect .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This draft reflects the changes we discussed during our call the other day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reflects\", does the participant \"changes\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We need responses or direction by no later than COB on Monday , October 30 , 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"We\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Andreas Bechtolsheim built a microcomputer ; Vinod Khosla recruited him and Scott McNealy to manufacture computers based on it , and Bill Joy to develop a UNIX - based OS for the computer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the participant \"microcomputer\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I remain convinced that if we can just get the facts in front of people they will modulate their approach .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"modulate\", does the participant \"they\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Senate increases NASA funding\"\nQuestion: In the event \"increases\", does the participant \"funding\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"President Bush loves him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the participant \"him\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"<< Upon the sixth of April , Alexander the Great was born .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"Alexander\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It was incorporated as a city on May 26 , 1955 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"incorporated\", does the participant \"It\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I use Miracle Cloth , they 're fantastic , just do n't use fabric softener or dryer sheets when cleaning them , it ruins their \" grabbing \" ability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ruins\", does the participant \"ability\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Cindy said Jaime has grown up very much .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grown\", does the participant \"Jaime\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another worrisome sign is that local Iraqi Sunni fundamentalists opposed to the US presence in Iraq have begun joining Monotheism and Holy War , and wearing its distinctive orange and black insignia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wearing\", does the participant \"insignia\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have my paralegal gathering the pleadings Enron requested .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"requested\", does the participant \"Enron\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I need something reliable and good looking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"something\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Bangs\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"First room had used tissues next to the bed and I requested it be rectified .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rectified\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"problem\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed working with you and wish you the best of everything .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"best\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"And the President becomes a Dictator , unrestrained by anything in the Constitution , backed up by the Armed Forces , which would be entirely under his personal control .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"becomes\", does the participant \"President\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He warned water levels could still rise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rise\", does the participant \"levels\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The impacts of climate change on the region and the globe are projected to increase substantially in the years to come . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"projected\", does the participant \"impacts\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Last week , Federal District Judge Lynn Hughes in Huston , Texas , threw out Wilson 's two - decades old conviction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threw\", does the participant \"Hughes\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This action accelerated the utilities ' move toward bankruptcy and forced the governor to move the state into the power - buying business . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accelerated\", does the participant \"action\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My last son , was born in Northern Ontario ....\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"son\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The pictures are broadcast at a rate of about 60 Hz , which is how fast they need to move for us to see them as a moving , flawless picture .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broadcast\", does the participant \"pictures\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I melt brass and cast it http://www.mikegigi.com/castgobl.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"melt\", does the participant \"brass\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There is no pleasure in having nothing to do ; the fun is in having lots to do and not doing it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"pleasure\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dr. Mann killed our pet\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"pet\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Thou art growing less doltish and more shrewd every day , Sancho , \" said Don Quixote .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"growing\", does the participant \"Thou\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ordered 1000 postcards , we normally order 5000 or more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They fixed the queso !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"queso\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They had a room with a $ 99 rate , which I booked .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Their Club sandwich looks tasty , maybe that 'll change my mind .... and a different server .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"mind\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On the one hand , the IPN report agreed \" Climate models generally predict that the temperature rises in the Arctic will substantially exceed the global rise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"exceed\", does the participant \"rises\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Should the Arctic Ocean become ice - free in summer , it is likely that polar bears and some seal species would be driven toward extinction , \" the report concluded .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"driven\", does the participant \"bears\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The days start to shorten & it gets even wetter , windier & colder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"start\", does the participant \"days\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"And the President becomes a Dictator , unrestrained by anything in the Constitution , backed up by the Armed Forces , which would be entirely under his personal control .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"becomes\", does the participant \"President\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Who does that ?!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"does\", does the participant \"that\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The good news is that all of this is temporary , because the evolution of international law has always adapted itself to reality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adapted\", does the participant \"itself\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"produce\", does the participant \"substance\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All he had to do for a complete victory was allow the military to go into Laos and Cambodia and finish off the shattered Communist forces .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finish\", does the participant \"forces\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He was trained to a harness / leash for outside time but he knew to use the litter pan inside .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"trained\", does the participant \"He\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bangs said these animals are not equipped to survive in the wild , however , and they all almost certainly have died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"they\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There was a change made in the coding for the delta position and this has somehow messed up the liq value .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"messed\", does the participant \"value\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I listed all of our ( sometimes mine vs. my wife 's favorites and priorities ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"listed\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Events change everyday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"Events\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a routine surgery for an ingrown toenail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Tamils feel that the proposed defense agreement between India and Sri Lanka would encourage Sinhala rulers to prepare for another war abandoning the current peace process\"\nQuestion: In the event \"encourage\", does the participant \"agreement\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Arial photos , loose connections to AQ Kahn and Libya make up the evidence that the group presented .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"presented\", does the participant \"evidence\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"post\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All you can do is take each section ( individual video ) and edit them together on software .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"edit\", does the participant \"them\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The price of crude oil on the international market hit a record $ 70.85 a barrel due to the vulnerability of oil and gas fields in the Gulf of Mexico .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hit\", does the participant \"$\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I presume you need the Pakistan base for rescue operations in case anything went wrong .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"presume\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"jill allen finishes her cpa today and she and her friends are going to party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finishes\", does the participant \"allen\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Hundreds of people are feared dead in Mississippi , and the Louisiana city of New Orleans is badly flooded .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"flooded\", does the participant \"city\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"But if -- there 's a painting on the wall in the Oval Office that shows a horseman charging up a steep cliff , and there are at least two other horsemen following .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shows\", does the participant \"painting\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"At least one expert believes China 's intentions might include a surprise attempt to circle the moon with astronauts before NASA 's planned lunar return .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"circle\", does the participant \"moon\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Founder Jack Smith got the idea of accessing e-mail via the web from a computer anywhere in the world .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"idea\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" It was about how he could humiliate her the most , \" prosecutor Dean Mandros said in closing arguments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Mandros\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He dated a beautiful young woman working on the campaign .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dated\", does the participant \"He\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Senate increases NASA funding\"\nQuestion: In the event \"increases\", does the participant \"funding\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You review and approve it , keep it on your desk , and I will come over and make the change at your desk on Monday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"review\", does the participant \"You\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I read an Article in Time magazine accusing the Iranian Government of being willing to start a nuclear war and I sympathise with the Article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"read\", does the participant \"Article\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i need to now get a job at house of pies b/c that is the only way to pay the bills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the participant \"bills\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Last week , Federal District Judge Lynn Hughes in Huston , Texas , threw out Wilson 's two - decades old conviction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threw\", does the participant \"conviction\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But if -- there 's a painting on the wall in the Oval Office that shows a horseman charging up a steep cliff , and there are at least two other horsemen following .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shows\", does the participant \"painting\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Across the board , the American military is stretched to the breaking point .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stretched\", does the participant \"military\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"MFJ Inc transformed our run down back yard into a place of beauty .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transformed\", does the participant \"Inc\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We need for interviewers to commit either to the morning ( 9 am - 12 pm ) or afternoon ( 2 pm - 5 pm ) complete session .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the participant \"interviewers\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But if -- there 's a painting on the wall in the Oval Office that shows a horseman charging up a steep cliff , and there are at least two other horsemen following .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shows\", does the participant \"painting\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"KENNEDY filed an opinion concurring in part , in which SOUTER , GINSBURG , and BREYER joined as to Parts I and II .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"opinion\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had this ridiculous celebrity stylist from LA named Derrick .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Cindy said Jaime has grown up very much .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grown\", does the participant \"Jaime\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Should the Arctic Ocean become ice - free in summer , it is likely that polar bears and some seal species would be driven toward extinction , \" the report concluded .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"driven\", does the participant \"bears\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In an apparently unrelated incidents , some eleven Iraqis were killed by snipers on Tuesday , including a group of police trainees in a bus near Hilla and two police in Kirkuk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"Iraqis\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In all , we received requests for 61 persons outside of Enron to host an eSpeak event .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"received\", does the participant \"requests\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The sample includes our \" caveat \" , so it should be fine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"includes\", does the participant \"caveat\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We oppose the use of sacred texts and religious traditions to deny legal equity to same - gender couples .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"oppose\", does the participant \"use\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The other ladies had a similar experience , both had nail polish on a couple of toes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"ladies\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Site made !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Site\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"they have their own website which you can easily find using any search engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"website\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He believed that the koran instructed that a jihadist should use the weapons used by the crusader .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"instructed\", does the participant \"koran\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We need to change the Prod Description fro the LME Product .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"Description\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I got this .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"this\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Site made !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Site\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Bangs\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The next day i took it to 2 auto shops and they both told me the same thing , engine is junk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Any of the tip - top places have great ice - cream , get them to mix it up .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"mix\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"An analysis of 65 bird species in the United Kingdom shows about one - third are laying their eggs four to seven days earlier than they did 25 years ago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"laying\", does the participant \"third\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I read an Article in Time magazine accusing the Iranian Government of being willing to start a nuclear war and I sympathise with the Article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"read\", does the participant \"Article\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I think it will help me very much in my role .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I detect the hissing lisp of the lying serpent in this article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"detect\", does the participant \"lisp\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"installed\", does the participant \"all\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The ACIA -- with participation by the United States , Canada , Denmark , Finland , Iceland , Norway , the Russian Federation and Sweden -- was begun in 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"begun\", does the participant \"ACIA\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Their screams changed , \" Dr. Fortier said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"changed\", does the participant \"screams\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had a great stay , your service was excellent and we will use you again !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"We\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Nobody thinks that there will be a lot of oil and gas in this part of the world , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"he\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Phenology studies an organism 's development and life cycle -- the pulse of life .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"studies\", does the participant \"Phenology\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"problem\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( '' We have three generations of martyrs : grandmothers , mothers , daughters . '' )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"We\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"<< Upon the sixth of April , Alexander the Great was born .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"Alexander\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The next day i took it to 2 auto shops and they both told me the same thing , engine is junk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The web site is\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"site\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"What is this irish tune called !?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"What\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"yea i guess but rabbits a easily escape a pen or another rabbit could get in there and that rabbit could be the opposite gender .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guess\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Last week , Federal District Judge Lynn Hughes in Huston , Texas , threw out Wilson 's two - decades old conviction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threw\", does the participant \"conviction\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The 99 - tonne cache of AK47s was to have been secretly flown out from a US base in Bosnia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the participant \"cache\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The United States goes into a war zone and evacuates a bunch of U.S. citizens ( most of whom were \" dual - citizens \" ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"evacuates\", does the participant \"bunch\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love the location and the apartment !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Your suggestion to introduce the concept discussed with one of the Lays is welcomed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"introduce\", does the participant \"concept\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They wanted to brainwash them and control them . ''\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brainwash\", does the participant \"them\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The US lost yet another helicopter to hostile fire near Habbaniyah in the Sunni heartland , but this time the crew was safe .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"helicopter\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"This year a newspaper claimed two UK firms were involved in a deal in which thousands of guns for Iraqi forces were re-routed to al - Qaeda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"re-routed\", does the participant \"thousands\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This message was cancelled from within Mozilla .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cancelled\", does the participant \"message\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Once upon a time ( in 2001 , to be specific ) , the Coca - Cola corporation built a bottling plant in a small and remote Indian village in the state of Kerala .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the participant \"plant\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Thanks to repeated deployments to Iraq and Afghanistan , recruiting is at an all - time low .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"recruiting\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Lo and behold , they replaced the screen ( which had to be ordered ) yesterday and did n't charge me a dime .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"charge\", does the participant \"me\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He believed that the koran instructed that a jihadist should use the weapons used by the crusader .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"instructed\", does the participant \"koran\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We oppose the use of sacred texts and religious traditions to deny legal equity to same - gender couples .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"oppose\", does the participant \"use\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The latter usually consider human beings a threat but the polar bear considers humans a snack , experts said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"considers\", does the participant \"bear\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The lady at pet smart said 4 hours , but on places on the net it says 10 to 12 hours .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"hours\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The FBI 's profile includes a US - based supporter of the militant islamists .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"includes\", does the participant \"profile\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" There have no business being there unless they are undermining Pakistan , '' says a Pakistani official .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"official\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He eats all of his grain but it just takes him a while to get it chewed because of the lack of muscle in his jaws .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eats\", does the participant \"all\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I tamed them in 4 days .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tamed\", does the participant \"them\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think it was in the Lincoln Square area but do n't quote me on that .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"quote\", does the participant \"me\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You need either a filter for each device except the DSL modem , or a whole home filter which filters all the jacks , except the one which the DSL modem connects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filters\", does the participant \"filter\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They called and worked with me to fix it so that it would look perfect .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There was a change made in the coding for the delta position and this has somehow messed up the liq value .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"messed\", does the participant \"value\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I prefer to devote most of my remarks to the broader picture of the region and its place in world events .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"devote\", does the participant \"most\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"YOU have to spend the time training .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"YOU\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the participant \"Google\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a question about McDonald 's Monopoly !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"question\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This action accelerated the utilities ' move toward bankruptcy and forced the governor to move the state into the power - buying business . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accelerated\", does the participant \"action\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At one point they told me the dog had been fixed , the next day it had n't .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"dog\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It boggles the mind that ANYONE can take at face value Bush 's claims to be a christian , yet many seem to do just that .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"boggles\", does the participant \"mind\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Every student of political science debates how you prevent an anti-democratic force from winning a democratic election and abolishing democracy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"winning\", does the participant \"election\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The price of crude oil on the international market hit a record $ 70.85 a barrel due to the vulnerability of oil and gas fields in the Gulf of Mexico .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hit\", does the participant \"$\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said it was the same tire , and verified this , after checking both the actual tire on my car and my service papers from earlier in the week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"He\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"As a result , your finances improve - and your newfound confidence could attract new love into your life .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"improve\", does the participant \"finances\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This action accelerated the utilities ' move toward bankruptcy and forced the governor to move the state into the power - buying business . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accelerated\", does the participant \"action\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Attached is my draft of a request for rehearing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"draft\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have extensive experience as a technical leader in the design and development of modeling and simulation software products , mostly for the oil and gas pipeline industry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Anyway , after much yelling and cussing I hung up , grabbed a cab , and went to Geno 's .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hung\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In the Oct. 31 letters , electricity producers told federal officials that if price caps were n't removed it would lead to a collapse of the energy market .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"caps\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" It was about how he could humiliate her the most , \" prosecutor Dean Mandros said in closing arguments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Mandros\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"About 1,200 Indian soldiers were killed during this phase of the conflict .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"soldiers\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Everything was done on a timely manner and things were cleaned and picked up every day when the crew was done .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"done\", does the participant \"Everything\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I need something reliable and good looking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"something\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I MAKE MONEY NOT DEAL WITH BROKERS \" Wow , can you believe in today s tough times this dealership would be looking for any way to move vehicles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"MAKE\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}]